Abbey Theatre collection, 1921-1995
Emory University
- Programs, 1921-1995 (bulk 1925-1942), Series 2; Box 2 - Box 8: folders 1-30
  - 1939 July 3 and following nights: MONTGOMERY, J.K, The Heritage (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - 1939 July 10 and following nights: SHIELS, George, Grogan and the Ferret (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - 1939 July 24 and following nights: MAYNE, Rutherford, Bridgehead (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - 1939 July 31 and following nights: MURRAY, T.C., Illumination; O'CONNOR, Frank, In the Train: Dramatised by Hugh Hunt (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - 1939 August 7, 8, 9: SHIELS, George, The Jailbird (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - 1939 August 10, 11, 12: ERVINE, St. John, Boyd's Shop (contains advertising insert for The Arrow) (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - 1939 August 14 and following nights: O'CASEY, Sean, The Plough and the Stars (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - 1939 August 21 and following nights: SHIELS, George, Paul Twyning (contains advertising insert for The Arrow) (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - 1939 September 4 and following nights: DEEVY, Teresa, The King of Spain's Daughter; O'CASEY, Sean, The Shadow of a Gunman (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - 1939 September 11 and following nights: SHIELS, George, Professor Tim (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - 1939 September 18 and following nights: ROBINSON, Lennox, Drama at Inish or Is Life Worth Living? (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - 1939 October 2 and following nights: O'CASEY, Sean, The Plough and the Stars: (contains advertising insert for The Irish Ballet Club) (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - 1939 October 9 and following nights: MURRAY, T.C., Illumination; O'CONNOR, Frank, In the Train: Dramatised by Hugh Hunt (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - 1939 October 16 and following nights: ROBINSON, Lennox, The Far-Off Hills (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - 1939 October 23 and following nights: ROBINSON, Lennox, The Whiteheaded Boy (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - 1939 October 30 and following nights: SHIELS, George, Give Him a House (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - 1939 November 6 and following nights: SHIELS, George, Give Him a House (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - 1939 November 13 and following nights: ERVINE, St. John, Boyd's Shop (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - 1939 November 20 and following nights: SHIELS, George, The New Gossoon (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - 1939 November 27 and following nights: SHIELS, George, Quin's Secret (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - 1939 December 4 and following nights: O'CONNOR, Frank, They Went by the Bus (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - 1939 December 11 and following nights: SHIELS, George, The Jailbird (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - 1939 December 26 and following nights: MacNAMARA, Brinsley, Look at the Heffernans! (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - 1940 January 8 and following nights: ERVINE, St. John, Mixed Marriage; SHAW, George Bernard, Village Wooing (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - 1940 January 15 and following nights: O'CASEY, Sean, Juno and the "Paycock" (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - 1940 January 22 and following nights: MURRAY, T.C., Spring; ROBINSON, Lennox, Bird's Nest (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - 1940 Feb 5 and following nights: MURRAY, T.C., Sovereign Love; ROBINSON, Lennox, The Whiteheaded Boy (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - 1940 Feb 12 and following nights: MAYNE, Rutherford, Bridgehead (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - 1940 Feb 19 and following nights: SHIELS, George, Paul Twyning (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - 1940 March 4 and following nights: CARROLL, Paul V., Shadow and Substance (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - 1940 March 11 and following nights: SHIELS, George, Give Him a House (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - 1940 April 1 and following nights: ERVINE, St. John, William John Mawhinney (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - 1940 April 8 and following nights: MONTGOMERY, J.K, The Heritage (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - 1940 April 15 and following nights: O'DALY, Cormac, The Silver Jubilee; O'CONNOR, Frank, In the Train: Dramatised by Hugh Hunt (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - 1940 April 22 and following nights: CONNOR, Elizabeth, Mount Prospect (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - 1940 April 29 and following nights: CONNOR, Elizabeth, Mount Prospect (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - 1940 May 6 and following nights: MacNAMARA, Brinsley, The Glorious Uncertainty (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - 1940 May 13 and following nights: MacADAM, Nora, Birth of a Giant; The Birth of the Infanta [ballet] (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - 1940 May 20 and following nights: SHIELS, George, The Passing Day (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - 1940 May 27 and following nights: MacNAMARA, Brinsley, Look at the Heffernans! (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - 1940 July 1 and following nights: SHIELS, George, The Jailbirds (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - 1940 July 8 and following nights: ROBINSON, Lennox, The Far-Off Hills (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - 1940 July 15 and following nights: HEPENSTALL, W.D., To-day and Yesterday (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - 1940 July 29 and following nights: HEPENSTALL, W.D., To-day and Yesterday (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - 1940 October 1 and following nights: SHIELS, George, The Rugged Path (souvenir programme containing author's biography and pictures of scenes from the play) (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - 1940 October 21 and following nights: SHIELS, George, The Rugged Path (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - 1940 October 28 and following nights: ROBINSON, Lennox, Drama at Inish or Is Life Worth Living? (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - 1940 November 11 and following nights: FEILDEN, Olga, Three to Go (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - 1940 November 18 and following nights: CONNOR, Elizabeth, Mount Prospect (Box 7, Folder 67)
  - 1940 November 25 and following nights: CARNEY, Frank, Peeping Tom (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - 1940 December 2 and following nights: CARNEY, Frank, Peeping Tom (contains notice regarding replacement of an actor) (Box 7, Folder 69)
  - 1941 January 20 and following nights: McHUGH, Roger, Trial at Green Street Courthouse (Box 7, Folder 70)
  - 1941 March 3 and following nights: SHIELS, George, The Summit (Box 7, Folder 71)
  - 1941 March 10 and following nights: D'ALTON, Louis, The Money Doesn't Matter (Box 7, Folder 72)
  - 1941 May 19 and following nights: WALL, Mervyn, The Lady in the Twilight (Box 7, Folder 73)
  - 1941 July 7 and following nights: ERVINE, St. John, Friends and Relations (Box 7, Folder 74)
  - 1941 July 28 and following nights: MAYNE, Rutherford, Peter (Box 7, Folder 75)
  - 1941 August 11 and following nights: MAYNE, Rutherford, Peter (Box 7, Folder 76)
  - 1941 August 25 and following nights: McGINN, Bernard, Remembered for Ever (Box 7, Folder 77)
  - 1941 October 14 and following nights: CONNOR, Elizabeth, Swans and Geese (Box 7, Folder 78)
  - 1942 January 12 and following nights: ROBINSON, Lennox, Forget-Me-Not: (contains insert announcing dates of upcoming plays (2 copies)) (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - 1942 January 19 and following nights: SHIELS, George, The Jailbirds (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - 1942 April 27 and following nights: SHIELS, George, The Fort Field (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - 1942 May 25 and following nights: LADY GREGORY, The Gaol Gate; LADY GREGORY, The Canavans (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - 1942 July 27 and following nights: MacCARTHY, B.G., The Whip Hand (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - 1942 August 3 and following nights: STUART, Francis, Strange Guest (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - 1942 August 10 and following nights: ROBINSON, Lennox, The Whiteheaded Boy (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - 1942 August 17 and following nights: ROBINSON, Lennox, The Whiteheaded Boy (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - 1942 September 21 and following nights: CONNOR, Elizabeth, An Apple a Day (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - 1942 October 26 and following nights: FITZMAURICE, George, The Country Dressmaker (contains insert announcing upcoming play) (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - 1942 December 1 and following nights: O'CASEY, Sean, Juno and the "Paycock": (contains two ticket stubs) (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - 1942 December 14 and following nights: ROBINSON, Lennox, The Clancy Name; ROBINSON, Lennox, Church Street (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - 1942 December 26 and following nights: SYNGE, J.M., The Playboy of the Western World (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - 1944 February 14 and following nights: CARROLL, Paul V., "The Wise Have Not Spoken" (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - 1944 August 28 and following nights: TOMELTY, Joseph, The End House (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - 1956 September 10: JOHNSTON, Denis, Strange Occurrence on Ireland's Eye (with details of Chekhow's one act comedy, The Proposal) (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - 1967 April 10: FRIEL, Brian, The Loves of Cass McGuire (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - 1980 April 10: O'CASEY, Sean, Red Roses for Me (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - 1983 March 17: FRIEL, Brian, Translations (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - 1988 June 27: Mac INTYRE, Tom, Snow White (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - 1990 February 20: O'CASEY Sean, The Silver Tassie (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - 1990 November 27: FRIEL, Brian, Faith Healer (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - 1991 November 27: BOUCHICAULT, Dion, The Corsican Brothers (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - 1993 June 30: FRIEL, Brian, Wonderful Tennessee (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - 1993 December 8: KEANE, John B., Sive (with associated Irish Times article) (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - 1993 October 6: MURPHY, Tom, Famine (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - 1994 February 15: McGUINNESS, Frank, The Bird Sanctuary (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - 1994 July 20: SHAW, George Barnard, The Doctor's Dilemma (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - 1994 December 27: SYNGE, J.M., The Well of the Saints (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - 1995 April 12: FRIEL, Brian, Philadelphia, Here I Come (Box 8, Folder 30)
- Other material, 1935-1941, Series 3; Box 8: folder 31-32
  - Eric Gorman correspondence
  - Correspondence, 1935-1941 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Abbey Theatre American Tour
  - The Abbey Theatre Players souvenir booklet, circa 1937 (Box 8, Folder 32)